Hello everybody, here we are in Barcelona at office hours and I'd like to introduce some
of the students in Internet history technology for the very first time it was taught. So here
we are. Hang on. So, give your name. Octavio. Okay. And you feel free to say something if
you want to your fellow students. Well, this has been nice to know Chuck and all the partners
in the course and nice to meet you. Okay. Hi, this is Magda Martinez. It's lovely to take
courses at Coursera and I hope you take it too. Okay. Hi, I'm Han and thank you for the
opportunity. Okay. Hi, my name is Janis and I loved it so I'll enjoy the courses. Hello,
I am Ivan. I'm happy to be here with Dr. Chuck and my fellow students. Okay. Hello, my name
is Andre and I love the course and I hope to have many more like this. Thank you. Hello,
I'm Jordi and I think it's a very good course. Okay. Okay. Okay. Thank you everybody. Oh,
here comes more traffic.